let questions = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question:
        " What is the relationship between the number of sides and the sum of interior angles in a polygon?",
      answer: "B. They are directly proportional",
      options: ["A. They are inversely proportional", "B. They are directly proportional", "C. They are unrelated", "D. They are equal"],
    },
  
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "How do the properties of a regular polygon differ from those of an irregular polygon?",
      answer: "C. Regular polygons have congruent sides and angles",
      options: [
        "A. Regular polygons have varying side lengths",
        "B. Irregular polygons have congruent angles",
        "C. Regular polygons have congruent sides and angles",
        "D. Irregular polygons have symmetrical angles",
      ],
    },
  
    {
      numb: 3,
      question:
        "Why do the interior angles of a triangle always add up to 180 degrees?",
      answer: "A. Due to the properties of triangles",
      options: [
        "A. Due to the properties of triangles",
        "B. Due to the Pythagorean Theorem",
        "C. Due to the sum of exterior angle",
        "D. It varies for different types of triangles",
      ],
    },
  
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "What is the significance of the sum of interior angles in a polygon?",
      answer: "B. It helps identify the type of polygon",
      options: ["A. It determines the area of the polygon", "B. It helps identify the type of polygon", "C. It determines the exterior angles", "D. It is unrelated to the polygon's properties"],
    },
  
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "How are exterior angles related to interior angles in a polygon?",
      answer: "B. They are supplementary",
      options: [
        "A. They are equal",
        "B. They are supplementary",
        "C. They are complementary",
        "D. There is no relationship between them",
      ],
    },

    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "What does the sum of interior angles in a polygon depend on?",
      answer: "A. Number of sides",
      options: [
        "A. Number of sides",
        "B. Perimeter of the polygon",
        "C. Number of vertices",
        "D. Area of the polygon",
      ],
    },

    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "How do convex and concave polygons differ in terms of angle measurements?",
      answer: "A. Convex polygons have all interior angles less than 180 degrees",
      options: [
        "A. Convex polygons have all interior angles less than 180 degrees",
        "B. Concave polygons have all interior angles greater than 180 degrees",
        "C. Convex polygons have equal interior and exterior angles",
        "D. Concave polygons have equal interior and exterior angles",
      ],
    },

    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "What role does symmetry play in solving problems related to sides and angles of polygons?",
      answer: "B. Symmetry simplifies angle calculations for regular polygons",
      options: [
        "A. Symmetry helps identify irregular polygons",
        "B. Symmetry simplifies angle calculations for regular polygons",
        "C. Symmetry leads to varying interior angles in a polygon",
        "D. Symmetry is irrelevant in polygon properties",
      ],
    },

    {
      numb: 9,
      question: " How can the Pythagorean Theorem be applied to solve problems involving right triangles within polygons?",
      answer: "C. To find missing side lengths or angles",
      options: [
        "A. To calculate the sum of interior angles",
        "B. To determine the number of sides in a polygon",
        "C. To find missing side lengths or angles",
        "D. To identify the type of polygon",
      ],
    },

    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "What is the exterior angle of a regular polygon equal to?",
      answer: "B. 120 degrees",
      options: [
        "A. 90 degrees",
        "B. 120 degrees",
        "C. 135 degrees",
        "D. 180 degrees",
      ],
    },
  ];
  